hey everybody welcome to this a2 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as I speak you ready
so today I'm gonna talk about the zoo
this is a topic that I really like
because I've always liked going to the
zoo I'm from San Diego which has one of
the best zoos in the world the San Diego
Zoo is famous for its animals and
exhibits I have many great memories from
the zoo and I hope that I get to go
again soon let's talk about the
different animals that you can find at a
big zoo like the San Diego Zoo let's
start with the most famous animal at the
zoo the panda bear this animal is many
people's favorite animal including my
wife's honestly I don't know why so many
people love pandas because they seem
pretty boring to me but I think people
just find them cute and funny
they're also popular because only
certain zoos are allowed to have them
most zoos around the world don't have
any pandas actually so that's another
reason why the San Diego Zoo is really
famous however I like other types of
bears more when I was in college I took
an animal biology class and for one of
my projects I studied the Sun bear this
is one of my favorite animals because
it's a really unique type of bear it's
smaller than other bears and it spends a
lot of its time climbing trees which i
think is pretty cool alright moving on
to Safari animals there are elephants
lions rhinoceroses giraffes and a lot of
other species these exhibits are some of
the most popular ones at many zoos
because these animals are so iconic
children love watching movies and
reading books about the wild animals in
Africa so of course they want to see
them in real life too I've always liked
the big cat animals such as lions but
honestly they don't do much when you see
them at the zoo they're always just
lying down or sleeping the elephants are
you
more active and it's always fun to watch
them swing their trunks around other
popular attractions at the zoo are the
monkeys gorillas and those types of
animals there are usually some different
types of small monkeys that are really
energetic and playful you can always see
them swinging from tree to tree and
playing with each other the gorillas on
the other hand are usually calmer but
sometimes they get really close to the
glass and look right at you it's
actually kind of scary because it feels
like they can reach out and grab you one
other exhibit that's usually pretty
popular is the Arctic exhibit this is
where they have the polar bears this
exhibit is way different from the other
exhibit because it's a completely
different climate it's ice rocks and
cold water some zoos also have penguins
as well which are some of the funnest
animals to watch they constantly jump in
and out of the water and you get to see
the cool way that they swim
penguins are definitely some of my
favorite animals
alright that's all for today leave a
comment down below and tell me what your
favorite animal is I'll see you next
time
[Music]
[Applause]